Jhal Jhal
Ajay Ko
Hello Hello Everyone Good Morning Good Morning in
front of you and today's second question of India's sochkar jaap is that
drain but we have
related question you can play mode you can
play with you can win mode with too much
luggage in the boot and realized that you can see
traffic behind you from near review
chilli powder is state president
and for this you have four options in front of you Gas
Limited has given roti behind in KBC Kaun Banega Crorepati in the
same way you keep doing it
and you will win prizes so the first option
is on your skin no it sanchet without real
review second was that news way rich
view all that kinda this I want real
change my
language to get on serial you too
and the first option is gas I will drive with is
jaat light on now out of these four
which option would you like to go for in Hindi I will do
tree for mother you have a
lot of stuff in your boot it can be put in a lot of board in akar
and you benefit from
whatever you give in your real minutes while
cutting actually like this  It seemed to you that
first let's look back from the rear view mirror
until you can't see the fear then
what will you do gown pastel
post will you still read then its first
option is no this is an excerpt without you have to listen
second is yes I that news which you will
keep on the side and after looking on the side it will
give that body the third option is yes I will
rearrange it to parcel van
and the fourth option is on your screen yes I will keep
guiding my thousand lines with the light on what do you think
which of these will be the best for you which is the
best option for you
as you know we have been having
a question start India by
17th February that you do it for a lot
and you become a councilor by winning
and then you will get what or will have to what
indicate saffron first ODI
match
that bike will be laid technology
classification and the winners will be called from our side
and Vinod will be informed about
his party whether bike ticket or
work cricket whichever he selects we will
provide him so that
I again  I repeat the question in the stomach,
your Vittu mast lagi in
Bullet and you feel that you can achieve
traffic behind from your rear view mirror work
still president is the first option in front of you
first option a you have no
objection certificate real review setting
of you have your say thank you with winners to get
real review third option ch2 yes I don't
rearrangement lagi to get par salary love
you and and faster yes I will drive with thousand
light on now you have to tell that you
I use it and out of this
what will be the correct answer jo bhi any man ko give the
right answer will
I mix it juice tinder lucky draw form
and left correct selected in lucky draw he will get
prize from us DJ best
price for stars bike shetty kept in
secret models classification it is your
choice a is what ever you want to love to take on how to all India gets president to humare chal raha hai
season 2 me humare jo pehla step
ka is mein humare updated hui aur ite
daily wage travels  From Wagah Border to
Kanyakumari, pin number five starts. Lady
drivers and Scheduled Tribes have lots of
experience of driving year after year.
Celebration Day where Lord I
participated in Delhi and edited and it's
all souls who invented a symbol of
women empowerment.
But now we say we will walk shoulder to shoulder, so let's come out to stand shoulder to shoulder
so that our road safety fund will
drive smart daily and
what can we say about women empowerment.
We did both of these together and ran
a rally of men from Kanyakumari to Bigg Boss and
our five winners
kept driving on different days. Porn
industry old, a dive deep Dakar to
Kanyakumari and he proved
that he is the best river and chicken
complete as much man complete and
as you can see, particular
screen question came,
this tweet a meaning image in the best
and you realize that you can see traffic police
lines from  Rear view mirror that deposit this
four option Pradesh first option inch take
notes unsafe the real tube skin options
page sa kam use meters to get real review
third option a b c d e s every year in her
luggage to get per salary love you for more
options pay side tribes of light on what
foods like please give answer plain mode on karo
ajay ko who
is the timing of 11.21 m the question
restless volume and stopped in oil and this
have to our time plot for this question
you can answer mode you can win more you can
participate mode and you can participate
and and 3000 1000 road tax in this going
on value 08 2013 hua
hai
ajay ko
hai plain mode and win more on
ki dera lots of idols time when they go
sadhu karne ka mausam time tarika backless
background sometime sometime pimple trishul
withdrawal view in to-do button time major
research rose and tagged  moment and our lady
driver our lady champion spiderman is
sentence health successfully completed bareilly
and should seek and drive a scan judgment
actually vikrant complaint in this regard to compliment
officer intimate scenes past
president and they have seen you always talk about
women empowerment and definition of
road safety is new body masti jaisi low time
[music]
nuvid
jaldi di haldi and withdrawal from his home
and welcome back gupta road accident at the
centre to avoid the ki vikalp
dawa date
hello friends and the maximum
unnatural death in india only 10 years every
day hui AIIMS on the road in which this
alternative not rudra avatar given by the
government of india i don't know how many
reports of not far when reports
last not means that not written by the
chronicles of system numbers with u have
150 more page numbers every year will u will
not exceed 131 towns  Like Roorkee, like
Plug Ramnagar, like Kashipur, Sachkhand and
conducts its small town will lose
every year on road, this is what we want, so
it is a good symbol for research,
now Lok Samiti on the center of the GDP,
accident will lose talk cemetery,
that and fair and no one likes Rupees, that now you will ask how
torch light bill, how because of these accidents on
property, this will not be lost here
according to Big Boss, first of all we take care of our big mind,
which is our dividend, our
dividend, after that this
chapter benefit will cause you loss of
property, we have property,
this is government property, question, accident on road,
our road and that guy is on road,
he is a student, time setting stop
and proved very hot, hence shocked, there will be roti,
what happens after that,
after roti what do we say, you have a little
road option, he has to make garment fair,
now the possession of tomorrow is the option of tomorrow by getting it
installed in India, by changing the personal in front, the option  The
texture that is going from it will come back now
all the world has been set and lost all the
best manpower a
trick of report has been done on setting always a that when
a sour sour young man goes away
then he goes omniscient and his family comes
because in India you have seen how many
numbers it depends on, an independence will be closed
now above the one who
comes immediately above a bed winner
how many different it is so 20 days can be avoided
that I am not a business wandered how can we want to take
road safety measures in our
daily life NRHM defeating bad omen fixed
replaying India's support is a question of reproduction in that
if you feel that your house looked
very good in the car but that treatment
and the Reliance traffic you will post then
your first option is notes without you can be used to
live without that
essay in retail if you if your body was
left very happy then
what will happen then the
cutter retire will rest more and always been
appointed in the turn on  Light and might happen at will
that not work shared limelight tijori inverter
not forget to blame for it produced
in not properly in god see the real
review website traffic and jobs please
share thank you
so please suggest a mistake in the road to
Bigg Boss you don't know your
entire family goes with you someone's
dreams go with you your family is not yours
your company can also be made by you
so are you working for them
that if seen in this world we are
not doing any pink actually we are
completing each other and when
we are completing each other yaar bhaiya
computing 19 that when health and computing is
not yes he is updating of his wife only and
completing a man and imprisoned his
profession his comfort completing the office of
all from his computing dead table
that these computing lots will be handed over
that time dub please special his role play
mode win more can select the from
now on